[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Дит. садок' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ようちえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ботанічний сад' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくぶつえん"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Парк розваг' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ゆうえんち"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Храм (буддійський)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おてら"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Овочевий' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やおや"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Спортзал' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいいくかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Посольство' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいしかん"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пожежна станція' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょうぼうしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відділ поліції' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けいさつしょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Музей' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はくぶつかん"
    }
]
